http://wxxi.org/privacy.html

Latest News
RCSD still waiting for some parents' preferences on hybrid model
Monroe County reports 678 new COVID-19 cases, and 9 additional deaths
County prepares for more COVID-19 cases, possible vaccine deployment
Programs
Second Opinion, Rochester International Jazz Festival, Arts InFocus, All WXXI Productions
Radio
Radio
Listen Live,
Information for
Students,
Kids, Parents,
Support WXXI
myWXXI, Membership, Corporate Sponsorship, Planned Giving, Volunteer, Vehicle Donation
Pledge Now!
Click Here to Donate
more...
Cultural Calendar
Home » Content
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which WXXI Public Broadcasting Council collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://wxxi.org, http://wxxinews.org, http://classical915.org, http://wrur.org, http://withradio.org, http://weos.org, http://reachoutradio.org, http://homeworkhotline.org, http://secondopinion-tv.org, http://artsinfocus.tv, http://exitedpodcast.org, http://innovationtrail.org or http://60secondscience.org websites (each, a "Site").
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
WXXI.org may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To run and operate our Site
We may need your information display content on the Site correctly.
To improve customer service
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
Except as described in the next section, "List Exchange Policy", WXXI does not share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
List Exchange PolicyWXXI uses shared lists to maximize the benefits it can provide through other local non-profit arts organizations. Your name and basic contact information may be exchanged for consideration with select organizations for a one-time use only. These organizations may attempt to contact you to promote a product or service that they offer. Such contacts from third parties will only be made with WXXI's consent, and WXXI will only grant its consent when WXXI considers the offer to be of potential interest and benefit to our members. No information will be shared about members' giving history. WXXI will not share, exchange, rent, or sell any of its lists to political parties or candidates for political office.
Electronic newsletters
If User decides to opt-in to our mailing lists, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Advertising
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. You may learn more about opting out of major ad networks at https://websitebuilders.com/tools/advertiser-opt-out/.
Google Adsense
Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Changes to this privacy policy
WXXI.org has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. This privacy policy was built
the web's favourite privacy policy generator.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.
This document was last updated on October 13, 2017
»
Support provided by:
Switch to mobile view.
Copyright 2020 - WXXI Public Broadcasting Council - FCC Public Files: WXXI-TV, WXXI-AM, WXXI-FM, WXXY-FM
